Wadsworth Family Papers 1790-1950
Wadsworth Family Papers
- Persons Who Worked for the Wadsworths as Farm or Day Laborers, 1831-1842; 5 ledgers
  - Farm Accounts and Hired Hands, April, 12 1841-June 9, 1841:; D (Box unwrapped)
Longfellow, I A Cruise boat line, Camden, Maine, Letter from August 28, ? Wadsworth,William Austin Thank you for trip. Box LWAW2 F 60 Shelf 26
Lowell, John, Horticulturist, Letter from March 10, 1829. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-Martin Brimmer
Fruit tree cuttings. Box L 1 F 1 Shelf 15
Lynch, James Rome, NY, Woolen manufacturer, Letters to (7) September 16, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; See Also subject heading "Sheep." Bk 61 Sh 27 use Index
Mahoney, Walter W, Editor of North American Review, Letters (3) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Articles for publishing Box J112E F 26 Sh 59
Mann, Horace, (1796-1859) Educator, Letter from November 30, 1844. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Manual Labor School; Education for young farmers. Box L4 Shelf 15
Manning, Thomas,; New York, Manning's Yacht Agency, Letters from (9) 1879. Wadsworth,Herbert (1851-1927) Yacht "Sea Witch." Box LHW1 Shelf 24
Manual Labor School, Geneseo, NY, Records (12) 1845. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Manual Labor School: letters; indentures; booklists. File cabinet 1 Drawer 2
Marcy, William Learned (1786-1857) Gov. NY; Sec of War, Letters from (5) 1851-1852. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Martin, Jack W, Capt., Avon Horse trader and Hunt member, Letters from (23) 1895. Wadsworth,William Austin Horses; Abel Farm. Box LWAW6 F 17 Shelf 26
Maslick, John, Six Land Agent in Ogden, Letters to (7) March 24, 1817+ Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Squatters on Six Family lands and Ogden leases. Bk 61 Sh 27 Use index
McKnight, L L Chicago IL, Letters from (4) 1879. Wadsworth,Herbert (1851-1927) Patent for steam powered steering device for ships Box LHW1 Shelf 24
McNabb, Andrew, Clerk for James, Letters to (65) September 26, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Pulteney Estate land in Caledonia and Braddocks Bay. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
McNair, Hugh, Canandaigua Settler and Ontario County Judge, Letter to July 24, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Office plans for Homestead. Bk 61 P 417 Shelf 27
McNair, Marion, Art student in India, Letters from (2) 1884-1885. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin India: description and travel; Thank you for money. Box LEAW2 F 1 Shelf 24
McNall, Neil Adams, author Agricultural History Genesee Val, Citations to the papers 1810-1850. Wadsworth,James, Wm. W, James S.
Agent-(See in footnotes)
Farming; Raising and produce. gen HD 1775 N82 G45
Means, Kilham F Boston, MA merchant, Bill March 18, 1840 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Clothing: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Clothing Sh 27
Meigs, Charles Delucena (1792-1869) Doctor, Letter from 5/9/1841. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Merchant and Miners Transportation Company, Letters from (3) 1879. Wadsworth,Herbert (1851-1927) Patent for steam powered steering device for ships Box LHW1 Shelf 24
Military Tract, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Military Tract Township Map. Map File #2
Miller, Anne F Lochland, Geneva NY Friend, Letters from (18) 1879-1891. Wadsworth,William Austin Personal. Box LWAW3 Fs 12-13 Sh26
Mills, William A Jr. (1777-1844) Mt. Morris, Letter to November 21, 1841 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Cattle: Fattening for market. Box LBk 1 P 124 Shelf 2
Milne, William (1843-1914) Principal Geneseo Normal School, Letters from (3) 1875-1877. Wadsworth,William Austin Normal School finances and Library matters. Box LWAW3 F 15 Shelf 26
Morgan, Edwin Denison (1881-1883) Governor of NY 1858, Letter from 6/22/1861. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Morgan, George Dayton (1864 -1937) General Railway Signal Co. Letters from (2) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Most Favored Nation Status for Spain. Box J112E F 21 Sh 59
Morgan, John Pierpont (1837-1913) Financier, Letter from September 12, 1881. Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Geneseo "Farmers" affair. Box LWAW3 F 16 Shelf 26
Morris, Lewis Rutherford MD (1862-1936) NYS Police Committee, Letter from April 17, 1917. Wadsworth,William Austin State Police Bill; crime in New York State. Box LWAW3 F 17 Shelf 26
Morrison, John W Boston Carpenter, Bills (5) 1878-1879. Wadsworth,William Austin Homestead vouchers for renovation by Sturgis and Brigham. File 1 Drawer 2 Fld (4)
Morse, Clarendon, Bookseller, Rochester NY, Bill December 11, 1841 Wadsworth,William Wolcott Farm account books, Example of collection's scope. Box V1 Books Shelf 27
Moscow Advertiser, and Genesee Farmer, Moscow NY Newspapers (11) 1817-1818 scattered issues. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Advertising for goods and services; News. Volume 2 and 3 Shelf 40
Mohawk and Hudson Railroad, Letter to October 20, 1839. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Railroad trip from Albany; conductor's behavior. Box LBk1 P 121 Shelf 27
Mure, S, Niece, Eaton Place S W, England, Letter Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal. Box LEAW2 F 3 Shelf 23
Murray, Charles (1806-1895); and Anne,; Elizabeth's family, Letters from (9) 1887-1900 and nd. Wadsworth,William Austin Family and friends. Box LWAW3 Shelf 26
Murray, Charles Augustus, (1806-1895) Elizabeth's husband, Letters from (6) 1883-1884. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Family and friends. Box LEAW2 Shelf 24
Murray, Charles Augustus, (1806-1895) Elizabeth's husband, Letters from (6) 1882-1884. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal. Box LEAW2 F 5 Shelf 24
Murray, Charles Augustus, (1806-1895) Elizabeth's husband, Letter from nd. [1851] Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Wadsworth, Elizabeth, notice of her death. Box LEAW2 F 4 Shelf 24
Murray, Elizabeth Wadsworth (1815-1851) Sister, Letters from (24) 1828-1845. Wadsworth,James S. and William W. Family and personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Murray, John and Sons, New York land speculator and importer, Letter to December 12, 1815. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Genesee Valley; Upper and lower areas compared. Bk 61 P 29 Shelf 27
Murray, John and Sons, New York land speculator and importer, Letter to February 17, 1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Ogden Church and School; Reverend and Mrs. Everett. Bk 61 P 497 Shelf 27
Murray, John and Sons, New York land speculator and importer, Letter to March 21, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Ogden settlers. Bk 61 P 83 Shelf 27
Murray, John and Sons, New York land speculator and importer, Letters to (33) October 4, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; Morris Tract; Fairfield (Ogden) accounts. Bk 61 Sh 27, use index
National Hotel, Washington DC, Bill February 15, 1838. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hotel lodging and food: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hotels Shelf 27
North, Henry P Hardware store, Bills (5) 1838-1840. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Hardware purchases: Examples of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Hardware Sh 27
O'Laughlin, John Callan, Pub. Army Navy Journal, and others, Letters from (10) 1924-1928. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. National Defense; Troop Strength. Box J112E F 22 Sh 59
O'Ryan, John F (1874-1961) Colonial Airlines President, Letters to and from (30) 1927-1928. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Airlines; Airport in Rochester, etc. Box J112E F 1 Sh 59
O'Ryan, John F (1874-1961) Colonial Airlines President, Letters from (2) 7/11/1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Rochester Airport; copy of letter to Mayor Martin O'Neil. Box J112E F 1
Ogden, David B. (1770-1829) Lawyer, assemblyman, Congressman, Letters to (7) October 2, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Indian Treaty; Hunger on Reservations in 1817. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow (1773-1844) NY Land speculator, Powers of Attorney, etc 1837-1838. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Indian lands and Treaty of 1838; Index in print and on film Lib Congress Microfilm
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow (1773-1844) NY Land speculator, Letters from (6) 1839. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Indian lands and Treaty of 1838; Index in print and on film Lib Congress Microfilm
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow (1773-1844) NY Land speculator, Letters to (2) June 5, July 1, 1840. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Contracts with Chiefs. Box LBk 1 P56-8 Sh 27
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow (1773-1844) NY Land speculator, Letter to March 24, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: New problems; Commissioner, etc. Box LBk 1 p 50 Sh 27
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow (1773-1844) NY Land speculator, Letter to March 20, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Talk with President, Sec of War. Box LBk 1 p 48 Sh 27
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow (1773-1844) NY Land speculator, Letter to March 20, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Legitimacy of the Indian Chiefs. Box LBk 1 P sh 27
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow (1773-1844) NY Land speculator, Letter to June 21, 1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Indian Treaty; Quakers' Christianizing the Indians. Bk 61 P 546 Shelf 27
Ogden, Thomas Ludlow and Joseph Fellows; The Ogden Company, Letter to October 5, 1838. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Compensation for land. Box LBk 1 P 30 Sh 27
Oneida Reservation, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Indian lands. Map File #2
Ontario and Steuben Counties, Map, printed 1790 's. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Phelps and Gorham's Purchase townships. Map File #2
Ontario and Steuben Counties, Map, manuscript 1790's. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Phelps and Gorham's Purchase settlements. Map File #2
Ontario and Steuben Counties, Map, manuscript 1790's. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Phelps and Gorham's Purchase Survey Map. Map File #2
Ontario Messenger, and Ontario Repository, Canandaigua Newspapers, 1810-1836 scattered issues. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Advertising for goods and services; News. Volumes 2 and 3 Shelf 40
Osborn, Henry Fairfield (1857-1935) Paleontologist. Letter from March 26, 1912. Wadsworth,William Austin Conservation education. Box LWAW3 F 29 Shelf 26
Paine, J W, Carriage maker, Norwich, England, Letter from November 28, 1876. Wadsworth,William Austin Carriage order. Box LWAW3 F 31 Shelf 26
Paine, James H Boston marine engineer, Letters from (2) 1879. Wadsworth,Herbert (1851-1927) Patent for boiler for steam steering device. Box LHWl Shelf 24
Parish, George, St. Lawrence County settler, Letter to September 7, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Emmigration of settlers to western US and Upper Canada. Bk 61 P 431-2 Shelf 27
Parker, E D Supervisor town of Arcade, Letters to and from (2) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Letchworth Park Reforestation. Box J112E F 19 Sh 59
Parmelee, Daniel, Connecticut Attorney, Letters to (3) 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wadsworth, John; family disagreement over estate. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Parsons, Chauncey, Blacksmith, Bills (3) 1838-1840. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Blacksmith services. Examples of vouchers' scope, Box V1 Blacksmith Sh 27
Patterson, Geo. Washington (1799-1879) NY Congressman, Letter from 5/28/1839. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Public affairs. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Pegram, Fred, Artist, Portrait, 1910. Wadsworth,Martha Blow Wadsworth, Martha Blow. Map file Drawer 20
Pell, Herbert Claiborne (1884-1961) Politician; Diplomat, Letters from (2) 1934. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Rhode Island Bridge Project. Box J112D F 9 Sh 59
Pellew, Henry E (1828-1923) NYC Charities Bureau Letter from 1881. Wadsworth,William Austin Regrets, Invitation to Hunt. Box LWAW3 F 32 Shelf 26
Penfield township, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Penfield lots. Map File #1 Main Set
Perkins, Elizabeth, Cotuit MA, Fiancee, Letters from (20) Wadsworth,William Austin Family and friends. Bx LWAW3 Fs 34-36 Sh 26
Pershing, John Joseph (1860-1948) General, Letter from 1914. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Cabinet Post of Secretary of War. Box J112D F 10 Sh 59
Pickett, Albert (1771-1850) and J.W. NYC educators, Letters to (3) 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) School teacher for Geneseo; Man he would like. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Pinchot, Gifford (1863-1946) Forester and Politician Letter from November 9, 1901. Wadsworth,William Austin Hunting. Box LWAW3 F 38 Shelf 26
Platt, Clarence M Corporation Counsel, Rochester NY Letters from (2) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Honeoye Reservoir. Box J112E F 16 sh 59
Platt, Jonas, Utica NY Federalist politician and judge, Letter to March 6, 1817. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Attorney for Geneseo; Asks assistance in finding one. Bk 61 P 195 Shelf 27
Post, Richard Bailey, Moscow settler and community leader Letters from (13) 1825-1828. Wadsworth,Daniel (1771-1848) Moscow NY and Livingston County affairs. Lib Congress Microfilm
Potter, Daniel Wand Woodruff Potter, Chili farmers, Lease 1848. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Chili land. Box C3 Fold. 9 Shelf 9
Potter, H B Government Accountant, Letter to August 29, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Indian Treaty of 1838: Compensation for Indian signators Box LBk 1 P 38 Sh 27
Prescott, Sarah, Wife of William Hickling, Letters from (2) 1865. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal. Box LEAW2 Shelf 24
Prescott, William Hickling (1796-1859) Historian. Letters from (10) 1845. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Love letters to Miss Austin. Box LEAW2 F 5 Shelf 24
Prince, William (1766-1842) Horticulturist on Long Island, Letter from November 1, 1831. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Fruit trees. Box L1 Folder 2 sh 15
Public Notice, Notices (33) September 20, 1815+. Wadsworth,James and William W. Wood and timber; stray animals; land use regulations. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Pulteney Estate, Maps 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Pulteney Estate land and townships maps. Map File #1 Main Set
Quincy, Edmund (1808-1877) Boston editor/author, Letters from (2) 1830-1831. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Randall, Henry Stephens (1811-76) Agriculturist educator, Letter from 12/5/1860. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Raymond, Henry Jarvis (1820-1869) New York Journalist, Letters from (2) 1862. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Read, John Meredith (1797-1874) Jurist, Letter from 5/16/1861. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Reed. William C Farm manager in Geneseo, Letters from (19) 1840-1843. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Farm news and accounts. Box L3 See Calendars
Richards, C Jones, Letters from (11) 1828-1831. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal; England. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Richardson, Robert, Millwright, Letters to (2) March 27; April 18, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Mill stones and wheel for flour mill on Conesus outlet. Bk 61 P 360, 375 Sh 27
Richardson, Robert, Millwright, Letters to (2) April 27; August 28 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Miller; asks help in finding one to run Conesus Mill. Bk 61 P 93, 147 Sh 27
Ritchie, Albert C (1876-1936) Governor of Maryland, Speech 8/14/1929. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Prohibition enforcement Box J112J F 6 Shelf 60
Ritchie, Cornelia W., Daughter of General James Samuel, Letter from Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal. See Also Adair, Cornelia Box LEAW2 F 10 Shelf 24
Roberts, T D Boston YMCA. Letter from February 25, 1875. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Request for funds. Box LEAW2 F 11 Shelf 24
Robertson, James, New York City wool merchant and trader, Letters to (2) March 26; April 22, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool; not selling, may sell off flock; washing wool. Bk 61 P 358, 379 Sh 27
Robinson, Joseph T ("Joe") (1872-1937) Senator, and others, Letters to and from (5) 1924-1928. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Tariff Commission and Tarriff Act. Box J112E F 29 sh 59
Rochester and Southern Railroad, Suit, September 12, 1895 Wadsworth,James Railroad right of way. File cabinet 1 Drawer 2
Rochester, Thomas Hart, President Rochester City Bank, Letters to (4) 1834-1835. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Bk 58)
Banking business. Box L8k 1 Sh 27-indexed
Rochester, Thomas Hart, President Rochester City Bank, Letters from (29) 1837-1843. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Banking business. Box L2-L3 See Calendars
Rogers, John H Supt. NYC Union League Club, Letters to and from (3) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Flag etiquette. Box J112E F 11 Sh 59
Rogers, Moses (1779-1821) Exporter, Letter to July 6, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Wool, three years shear to sell; view of washing on back. Bk 61 P 405 Shelf 27
Roosevelt, Edith Kermit (1861-1948). Wife of Theodore, Letters from (11) 1888-1901. Wadsworth,William Austin Personal. Box LWAW3 F 49 Shelf 26
Roosevelt, Kermit (1889-1943) Teddy's son; Soldier Letter from July 18, 1917. Wadsworth,William Austin Boone and Crockett Club; Resignation as Secretary. Box LWAW3 F 48 Shelf 26
Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) Civil Service Commission. Letters from (11) 1893. Wadsworth,William Austin Boone and Crockett Club; Worlds Fair. Box LWAW3 F 50 Shelf 26
Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) Governor NY and other, Letters from (6) 1900. Wadsworth,William Austin Forest, Fish and Game Commission problems. Box LWAW3 F 55 Shelf 26
Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) New York City office, Letters from (4) 1911-1912. Wadsworth,William Austin Health of wife. Box LWAW3 F 54 Shelf 26
Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) Governor of NY 1898, Letter from Wadsworth,William Austin Hunt: turns down an invitation to come to Geneseo.
Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) Governor of NY 1898, Letters from (12) 1899-1900. Wadsworth,William Austin Politics. Box LWAW3 F 52 Shelf 26
Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) 26th President of US, Letters from (5) 1901-1903. Wadsworth,William Austin Politics; Invitation to the White·House. Box LWAW3 F 53 Shelf 26
Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) Assist. Sec. of Navy, Letter from March 26, 1898. Wadsworth,William Austin Spanish-American War. Box LWAW3 F 51 Shelf 26
Root, Elihu (1845-1937) Statesman and Diplomat, Letter from 1914. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Senatorial race. Box J112D Fl1 sh 59
Roulet, John S. Agent for six family the Hague, Letters to (16) October 4, 1815+. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Six Family lands. Bk 61 Sh 27 use index
Ruggles, Charles (1789-1865?) Letter to January 1, 1842. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Allegany County; Patterson Tract. Box LBk 1 P 69 Sh 27
Rush township, Map 19th century Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Rush settlers and land owners. Map File #1 Main Set
Sabin, Charles Hamilton (1868-1933) Banker and Republican Letters (3) 1924. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Stone Mountain Monument Box J112E F 15 Sh 59
Sabin, Pauline, NYS Republican Committeewoman, Letters to and from (10) 1923-1916 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Child Labor. Box J112E F 4 Sh 59
Sabin, Pauline, NYS Republican Committeewoman, Letters to and from (3) 1924 Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Constitutional Amendments. Box J112E F 6 Sh 59
Sabin, Pauline, NYS Republican Committeewoman, Letters to and from (25) 1926-1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Politics. Box J112E F 28 Sh 59
Sabin, Pauline, NYS Republican Committeewoman, others Letters from, etc. (5) 1926. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. World Court. Box J112E F 37 Sh 59
Sargent, John T Boston MA, Letters from (4) 1828. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Personal. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Schuyler, Charles E New York City Attorney, Letters from, etc. (4) 1926. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Wadsworth Trust Co. proposed for Wadsworth Building. Box J112E F 35 Sh 59
Scientific American, Letters from (8) 1879. Wadsworth,Herbert (185i-1927) Advertisement costs for improved steering device. Box LHW1 Shelf 24
Seely, Jonas, Letter to 1835 Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Cattle on Genesee flats doing well. Box LBk 1 P 100 Shelf 2
Seven Nations Farm, Bills (3) Wadsworth,William Wolcott Barn construction materials, labor and costs. File Cab. 1 Drawer 2
Seymour, Erastus B and Pardon C. Sherman, Buffalo NY, Lease for 4 years 1845. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Buffalo land. Box C2 F 15 Shelf 9
Seymour, Horatio (1810-1886) Governor of NY 1852, Letter from May 19, 1852. Wadsworth,James S. (1807-1864) Politics. Index in print and on microfilm Lib Congress Microfilm
Sheffield, James R (1864-1938) Ambassador to Mexico, Letters to and from (10) 1925-1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Mexican situation; Personal. Box J112E F 20 Sh 59
Sheffield, James R (1864-1938) Ambassador to Mexico, Letter from 1934. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Personal. Box J112D F 12 Sh 59
Sheriff of Ontario County Letter to January 4, 1819. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Prisoner James Forbes; burglarized stores New Years nite Bk 61 P 470 Shelf 27
Sherman, William Tecumseh (1820-1891) General in Civil War, Letters from (6) 1880-1881. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Personal. Box LEAW2 F 12 Shelf 24
Shirreff, Patrick, Scottish author, traveler and agriculturist, Letter to June 19, 1835. Wadsworth,William Wolcott
Agent-(Book 58)
Farming in Geneseo mentioned in book by Shirreff. Box LBk 1 P 59 Shelf 27
Sigourney, Lydia Howard (1791-1865) Author, Letter to January 4, 1843. Wadsworth,Elizabeth (1815-1851) Genesee Valley History; info on "Big Tree" for her book. File Cab. 1, Drs 1 and 2
Silliman, Benjamin (1779-1864) Educator and scientist Letters from (44) 1825-1848. Wadsworth,Daniel (1771-1848) Personal and Business Index in print and on microfilm. Lib Congress Microfilm
Sister Semplicia, Boston nun, Carney Hospital, Letter from December 15, 1884. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Donation, Thank You. Box LEAW2 F 13 Shelf 24
Six, Cornelius C, Dutch owner of Henrietta lands, Letter to August 29, 1816. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Henrietta and Riga lots Bk 61 P 147 Shelf 27
Smith, Alfred Emanuel (1873-1944) Governor of New York, Letters to (3) 1925. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Bond Issue for State Construction Projects. Box J112E F 2 Sh 59
Smith, Alfred Emanuel (1873-1944) Governor of NY 1922+, Letter from 1931. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Personal. Box J112D F 13 Sh 59
Smith, E F Rochester NY Commission Merchant, Bills (3) 1840. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Groceries and provisions: Examples of vouchers' scope, Box V1 Groceries Sh 27
Smith, Henry and Son, Boston MA, Bill March 2, 1840. Wadsworth,William Wolcott Gloves: Example of vouchers' scope. Box V1 Clothing Sh 27
Smith, William Lord, Boston MA, Letter from Wadsworth,William Austin Hunting in Mexico. Box LWAW3 F 62 Shelf 26
Spellman, Francis Joseph (1889-1967) Cardinal; Archbishop, Letter from 1947. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Donation to Alfred E. Smith Memorial. Box J112D F 17 Sh 59
Sperry, James, Surveyor; Family Agent in Ohio, Letters to (40) 1836-1842. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Ohio lands in Hardin County; Hog Creek Prairie. Box LBk 1 Sh 27 Index
Stetson, Cushing, National Farm School Expansion Project, Letters to and from (2) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Agricultural Education; See Also Manual Labor School. Box J112E F 8 Sh 59
Stevens, Jacob and James Sperry, Henrietta land owners, Letter to February 9, 1818. Wadsworth,James (1768-1844) Henrietta: asking they keep the name of C.C. Six's wife. Bk 61 P 327 Shelf 27
Stillin, J B Caledonia, Letter to December 9, 1839. Wadsworth,James S (1807-1864) Quarry on Street Farm in Caledonia. Box LBk 1 P 41 Sh 27
Stowell, George M Boston YMCA, Letter from March 13, 1885. Wadsworth,Emmeline Austin Donation, Thank You. Box LEAW2 F 14 Shelf 24
Strang, Arthur Innis, son of Geneseo lawyer, and others, Letters (4) 1927. Wadsworth,James Wolcott, Jr. Governor's race: asking him to run. Box J112E F 14 Sh 59
Sturgis, John H (1834-1888) Architect, Letters from (3) 1882. Wadsworth,William Austin Howland, S.S. House plans. Box LWAW3 Fs 71-72 Sh26